allr so welcome next Speaker hen
nounder
cpoare Talk
usingity enty resolution systemk
yes thank you for me today so talks
already
presentation
Willes one oflees ce ST
inir our company because WEC
companybody
talking I show little B how we can
traditional Systems
together bitc conference
Berin i and  I was asking
myself Systems everything what we did
before but much easier and out effort
that we also I
you lines h so that more than 80% of
enterprises will have used generative ai
APIs or deploy generative ai enbl
applications
2026 little
bit one usee small
in  the entire organization will come
later to that also and then another big
thing that we quite often in our
previous companies is that data privacy
and security is a big concern when
dealing with data so we are dealing
mostly with Person data sometimes also
company data and we  speak always about
gdpr and your customers ask oh you are
in the
cloud
for expected
language
[Music]
Mod si mark will to concentrate
onot because Personal data
weatots
helpot challenges so agenda for to
so
will
esams Problem in bigger
enterprisesty  resolutions in maybe who
enty
Resolution many
conferen one
US enty
Resolution
next generation you all know it as I
heard so we don't need to speak too much
about that and then we define the new
term which is called identity so we
heard Graph from Microsoft  we have many
other cases and I will show you what
that means I will do a live Demo we have tomorrow
product product Lunch product launch
sorry so maybe you can support us we
will launch what show you today and have
conclusion and future implications and
we can discuss  a lot I have time
for example scenario i will show you
today is about an insurance company
thats to use an LM power chatb to make
it easier for
customers services
customer qu contract what contract value
what in the
contract to have quickiable
answersat so hallucinate becauseic
ofes  new
IDE 75% of thes answer human
interaction only more complic Update
dataong
in human
so
LM priv data
Problem general
was problem because germanly English
because Steven
Scotland anotherlo Jordan natural whole
company speaks English also most of our
custom speak eng
information yester
contct contct
I have  to feed the LLM with uptodate
information then if we  just take it out
of the box so I log into SH
GPT i ask a question about my contract
how should it be able to answer that
right doesn't have any access to my
internal information and so we need to
somehow connect it we heard about  REC so
coming to that
later and we privacy concern so what
happens with the data that I enter
me Internet
data discussion we
so okay okay nothing discuss
today your data and insurance contract
you don't want that ends up in so not
another
custom
Cheng
%  ies faster Users responses so that is
coming already live and we
neglect now coming to the problem of
customer data
so Who of you has more than different
sourcesustomer syem
[Music]
tot normal
because we could medicalb we could
education database Loyalty database
employe
database you can  have your customers in
sales force you can have customers in
your internal system maybe
youely sy
[Music]
eh
databasesustomers
in
est
rec datting
fragmented
vi complete customer profiles exuse
of fin
syer
ty in
Gerer delivery
so h can also see so all dots records
from one  of databases all the
person source
customer and
last
person so many
records
[Music]
interconnected
om inons
information of financialartment Ex
disconnected
analyartment
ceonders
s the
you different sources so customer
data employee
data
imagine customer
emploe may betteren so all red dots
connected each other
dots so one Department only see a small
portion of
graph real problem so h  that would mean
we have 10 different customer profiles
for that one person interesting also
have Investors so Investors 10 customer
profiles because a big amount of
customers if for internal use and you
want to optimize and for example don't
want to send that customers Marketing
Emails  per
week a different
case we come to compliance risk
something which the last two days I
rarely heard only so I mean we talk a
lot about technology here but the big
problem is also if we don't only deal
with product data but also customer data
we have our nice data privacy
authorities h in Europe mean in the US
happening on the one for technical
perspective challenge because I mean we
that ai Act data it creates more work
for us and makes everything a little bit
harder I don't know you know  article 15
gdpr that means in the
if you want to know which data  company
about you you can because article 15
please tell what
dat Case last month company that inst
solar system on
theof
information information passw
[Music]
answer can be quite big so the first
thing is respond with
days the second thing also talk about
search and about  databases B technical
challenge you can tell delete
dat Ex
tricky
[Music]
EXP we
TLE 9% our data personal
data Person del data
in record record g go back
syem means dat in all
systemst tricky
Ofen so
next maintaining data accur
[Music]
never working
AGC
owing lot of amazing examp the
technology used also morning using for
indes in
alsoage
dat
Last
haly
Challenge what happensuse
data
[Music]
in
y
takesaly invs
[Music]
understanding the
custom
generationely most of our
generationting
h completely different
sol
solutions
data
res solution
dat  enty
[Music]
resolutions create reside
linking different representations
of real entity across various data
sources SLE database
so one view on the person imagine that
GRA h
one Clusters so like that could be
addresses for
example and entity Resolution no matter
how you implemented you really get  that
unified
view so now you could say and many
people with we speak the first time why
is it so complex so I mean it sounds
easy and if we talk now about llms why
don't I just ingest all my data let's say
1 million records  and
that maybe will solutions also outcome
not
predi each time would that
outcome little B
res BIC
Disc
res compare record other
recan
scenario Million record
means more that more
Problem BEC also the more expensive
becomes so I will now speak about scale
speed and cost of operation
of scale so yesterday evening I
created
snail more
data
[Music]
pt can Magic but
needun in real
time interesting so go beyond million
records most systems will
resp ch RECS
per databas ne
Neptun
backilable and always created problem
because all slow down when you too much
data
Problem Deal real data
chenge
Speed ​​in batch data and at the same time
in Realtime data so it could be that you
have million records at and at the same
time don't know 100 Records per second
also the real data comes in
so pyt unif
data
aex might simple because you just do it
over and over  again can be costly but
would work but what at the same time
searches on the data so one of our
customers back
CL to really decide someone canch
invoice within 300 milliseconds you need
to tell us the credit history of that
customer
Ex
datail Prof understand what so  next
Challenge worked l in infrastructure
before
J was Problem elastic
search
in date
coming us
in
sy so
what may Comp Cheng
[Music]
D so have change GRA Date works but have
TRAV GRA to get a d and that means quite
of
recur
longer before the longer  it takes
Effy go back the
CL of pressure
in so how can we scale the C amount of
data cost ingestion cost of storage
alsoch
[Music]
ind in real cost of
storage cost of operation maintenance we
morningatess Systems so when we started
the company IED because  before I
operated 5000 Hardware Servers Teams i
anymore getting up during because hard
fail serversver
meansone
sign new sy
Backup means Backup not createip F
Upload
work in many technology
project
elopess
also the time of recovery point
objective Recovery objective so System
breaks down also morning the PL  the
system living so really  like that
because like THR it over runs take
anymore will come back
so now we come to the components of an
entity Resolution system data ingestion
Layer data standardation
important show you later the matching
engine which really does all the
intelligent matching entity database in
our
case3 so  you can also it many other
processes AP
Layer May but
Sim
pointrib
schem struct dat normal data means
normal normalound
before data the matching TR
normal Filter Test
dat AP
ler don't any
love love
only amount of
data to si pay all so s request
Set  syst at our data understand data how
good data ist make an architecture
design how system should be does it need
B does it need real time things I select
the algorithm so for Name matching for
example we often use phonetics together
with distance
algorithms Def entity Model so  is it
about person is about household about
company
crucialustom never
enty because Users yes User natural
personone using my
app question system
integration
backupsingestingpling our techny
architecture of our producted quickly
Show so complely Server means data on
S3 Indexes in dynam
DB dynamob quite expensive ingest so
know  so would  90% of the C
usingest
dynamob LDA Services API Gateway
functionality Amazon we
havearch wen customers de environment
mostly
[Music] it
easy infrastructure set can Magic in
LDA
functions matching
works
oach
vectb GRA DBS like
identity Graph
Microsoft
simpleb making it complicated also
technolog however
all  approeser
in
in Slow fored do
alsoingue Ex
hol
matching attributes US
work let Look time
long okay okay Perf
so customer dat comp meanseses
so always combination of Attribut
andty Resolution so always
Match different attributes at the time
so notain dat
ofth it could
be ID number enough  but ID numbers in
US
Problem so when you for example register
for service it might have happen to you
that you wanted to sign in again and it
didn't work because Email tY for example
delivery so we have deal with
data R on the customer create  cle data
if deal with Person have big problem
that move get
marriedorcrib
ur Comp 10 20 years that data changes
AOT
understand new data constantly that
might transaction data
might Mail back and have change
that
soing identy
[Music]
res  system
can one of our competitors can open
sourcees
matter
System Main
identi
responsesty soluty Resolution
System identy
SLE source of TR for data no matter
where you
datanowflake sal identif record always
comingty Resolution system and that can
beleid all
systemsid one
customer does matter dat in
System
s  you can combine technologies use
identity identities can vector database
databasees Demo
V datab PDF
FF
contract so
[Music]
comcing my
system s Müller
okay will just stop that we can read it
so that fetch data from the identity
Resolution system
and in nice way so big  challenge that we
had in the beginning used Open and the
responses quite every time on the
weekend we
switch5 sonet and we get extensive
responses so that might be too long for
normal User but you goes so recogni
Person its different addes for that
person different phone numbers  email
addresses it even knows about
employment that was generated Test
dat what
ofest and now it tells me what is all in
there which is really nice and I can
also ask questions like tell me about
enoance
contract now already goes again to the
entity Resolution System so  there we
have  one field which is urance contract
and that a link of it will
[Music]
ation
PDF vector
databased information
latest pH
number as I could not reach
sopie and now will go back to the entity
Resolution System again look for the
data and will tell me the  phone numbers
of the different cities before one in R
maybe
could Demo so
so
conclusion running out of
time so
identityowm private information about
personss combine all technologies
what
in abilities tool based on
theuse Tools in best combination
possible I really like the outcomes very
really between the  different LM so you
have to test and afraid what happens
when like son 35 will beced out so have
adjust
again the data accessible
User API created SDK us in chain makes
it EAS complely Schema and will
automatically
adjust comination of LMS and specialized
systems make it really  Diff make it
really easy to get data from different
sources and Cre unif view h so Best
Practices
[Music]
technology for usee vector database it
makes s vector database GRA database MAK
ed increctness also so TR
out successful imple enty resolution
systemer
millionend because challenging will
may online
aupcation
linking party
exactly  the same matching relevant
data unification go step further also
doesn't only take will dlicates but also
similar data in
it thanks a lot thank you and tomorrow
we launch on productun So if you want to
support us the QR code and thank you
than